<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wes Cunningham</title>
    <link>http://wescunningham.net/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wes Cunningham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 21:47:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://wescunningham.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;m looking for</title>
      <link>http://wescunningham.net/post/looking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 21:47:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wescunningham.net/post/looking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;let me describe what I&amp;rsquo;m looking for in a relationship. I like my anonymity. I like my autonomy. I have no time or desire to tweet or chat or youtube or golf or watch football or put my clothes up. I DO have time and desire to make songs here and there - which, honestly, works great for me. I need something to rub against. Makes the gold, golder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was I saying? Yes. Us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to share joy and hope and love and peace. I do not want to get popular or political or preachy. The three p&amp;rsquo;s. No thanks Pal!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t want a reality show. Don&amp;rsquo;t want pics of me everywhere. Don&amp;rsquo;t want a record deal, don&amp;rsquo;t want to play in your back yard. ( although&amp;hellip;$ talks!). Kidding. Kinda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got &amp;lsquo;old man&amp;rsquo; opinions about everything from christian music to waiting in lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear about cool people you know. I don&amp;rsquo;t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got enough on my plate. I&amp;rsquo;m happy with my life. I love my family. I like working outside with my hands. I like making music in the basement. I want to spread love and hope and gratitude for life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good enough? Good. Don&amp;rsquo;t buy anything. I would be a terrible rich person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I&amp;rsquo;d really hate myself!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, now I&amp;rsquo;m just stalling because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to make dinner&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi</title>
      <link>http://wescunningham.net/post/hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 21:28:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wescunningham.net/post/hi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was young and ambitious&amp;hellip; and naive&amp;hellip;I somehow got a record deal with Warner Brothers records. This was something different. It was like winning the lottery. Or almost winning the lottery. I flew around a lot.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
After a while I became very self-conscious and neurotic. And I really wanted to BE who these good people wanted me to be. But&amp;hellip; I didn&amp;rsquo;t sell any records. And then we all mooned Chris Issak. Also Napster came and fired all the record guys and that was it, (I did make a second record for Warners that was never released).
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
So, tried again. Moved to california. Made a couple things and drove myself to New york AND BACK following some other band&amp;rsquo;s tour bus. Its what&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;lsquo;touring&amp;rsquo; and its really hard when its just you. or me. Anyway, that was ridiculous and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to spend my life that way anymore. I missed the earth so much, I missed my wife. it&amp;rsquo;s lonely out in space&amp;hellip;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Moved back home to Texas. Floundered around a bit. Taught spanish. Had kids and took random jobs. Sometimes i&amp;rsquo;d put my antenna up and write down what I heard. sometimes i&amp;rsquo;d just open the door a little and everything would start falling on me. but, sometimes a G chord just sounded like a G chord.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Somewhere in there I made a movie with some friends called SIRONIA. It was a trip and I loved every minute of it. Acting was harder than I thought and really wish I could have a second shot at it. I feel like I &amp;ldquo;get it&amp;rdquo; now. But whatever. It was really fun to imagine something and see it created. Heady. And then the circus left. Again.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
So, now a days&amp;hellip;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;m in a productive period artistically. Its been a good wave. Got with some pals in nashville one day last month and made ALASKA, (same dudes as C.I. mooning days). It was a joyous experience.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The feeling of that day. Of these 5 little songs, has opened something up for me. a new creative energy. Don&amp;rsquo;t know why. Or why now. Don&amp;rsquo;t know, but I love it when its on. I kept it off for years thinking that would make me happy.
I work during the day. I do whatever. Last week me and my 12yr old built a fence for some friends of ours. I&amp;rsquo;m rehabbing a 100 yr old house i bought for nothing because it was literally falling over. We live really simply so I don&amp;rsquo;t need to make stupid money. Emilie&amp;rsquo;s in school and I get to hang out with my boys a lot. And in the &amp;ldquo;in between moments,&amp;rdquo; (like now, my kids are all plugged in..), I make music.
I sing songs into my phone. and imagine them with new clothes on. I get lost in the cloud of a new song and that&amp;rsquo;s a splendid feeling.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
And I make CDs for my friends and they say they like them and then I feel sad for some reason so I write more music. It&amp;rsquo;s like this; I played the new recordings for my 10 yr old. and I was watching his face and I was conducting the music as he sat there with head phones on and I was yelling,&amp;ldquo;Hear this part take off?!&amp;rdquo;, and I found myself beaming. That&amp;rsquo;s how I want to share music. If you like it for background music, thats fine, but I don&amp;rsquo;t relate to that.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Thats pretty much it. Thanks for listening to my music. I hope you feel happy and at peace when you listen to ALASKA. I mean it. I gotta go beat up some kids.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Wes Cunningham&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>